{
    "German months": {
        "1": {
            "front": "January",
            "back": "Januar",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "2": {
            "front": "February",
            "back": "Februar",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "3": {
            "front": "March",
            "back": "Marz",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "4": {
            "front": "April",
            "back": "April",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "5": {
            "front": "May",
            "back": "Mai",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "6": {
            "front": "June",
            "back": "Juni",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "7": {
            "front": "July",
            "back": "Juli",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "8": {
            "front": "August",
            "back": "August",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "9": {
            "front": "September",
            "back": "September",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "10": {
            "front": "October",
            "back": "Oktober",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "11": {
            "front": "November",
            "back": "November",
            "is_new": true
        },
        "12": {
            "front": "December",
            "back": "Dezember",
            "is_new": true
        }
    }
}